Guide to the Douglas Killgore video materials, 1911-2013 UA 405
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Media
  - Jenifer Bratter, Parts 1 and 2, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-09-16 (Box 6)
  - CORRUL; Bratter redos, (DVD), 2009-09-16 (Box 6)
  - Vinod Khosla / Punditry/Invention, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-09-17 (Box 6)
  - Rice Alliance, McNair, 1 of 2, (DV), 2009-09-17 (Box 6)
  - Rice Alliance, Cam 2, (DV), 2009-09-17 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines, Part 1, (DVD), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Aniruddh D. Patel / Grown of Music Neuroscience Rough Dub, no PowerPoint, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #1 Speakers, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #1 PTT, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #2 Speakers, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #2 PPT, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #3 Speakers, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #3 PPT, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #4 Speakers, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #4 PPT, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #5 Speakers, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #5 PPT, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #6 Speakers, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Emerging Disciplines Symposium, #6 PPT, (DV), 2009-09-18 (Box 6)
  - John McDevitt, (DVD), 2009-09-28 (Box 6)
  - Lab in backpack, (DV), 2009-10-01 (Box 6)
  - Tony Kushner, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-10-14 (Box 5)
  - PLS C 1 #1, (DV), 2009-10-14 (Box 6)
  - PLS C 1 #2, (DV), 2009-10-14 (Box 6)
  - President's Lecture Series, C 2, R1, (DV), 2009-10-14 (Box 6)
  - PLS C 2, #2, (DV), 2009-10-14 (Box 6)
  - Reactions to the Fall of the Berlin Wall (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-10-27 (Box 6)
  - James Cuno #2, (DV), 2009-10-27 (Box 6)
  - Klaus Weissenberger / Reactions to the Fall of the Berlin Wall, Pt 1, (DV), 2009-10-27 (Box 6)
  - Klaus Weissenberger / Reactions to the Fall of the Berlin Wall, Pt 2, (DV), 2009-10-27 (Box 6)
  - Carlos Vid Soc Poster, (DV), 2009-10-27 (Box 6)
  - Rice #1a Cuno, (DV), 2009-10-27 (Box 6)
  - James Cuno / The Promise of Museums, Part 1, The Promise of Science(2), Rice Media, (DVD) 2009-10-27/2009-10-29 (Box 6)
  - James Cuno #1, (DV), 2009-10-28 (Box 6)
  - James Cuno #2, (DV), 2009-10-28 (Box 6)
  - James Cuno #1, (DV), 2009-10-29 (Box 6)
  - James Cuno #1, (DV), 2009-10-29 (Box 6)
  - Tom Lange / Will Pringles Fly? (2), Rice IT, (DVD), 2009-10-30 (Box 3)
  - Anthony Shadid, Tape 1, (DV), 2009-11-07 (Box 5)
  - Anthony Shadid, Tape 3, (DV), 2009-11-07 (Box 4)
  - Carrie Masiello (Janice Trojan) video recording, (DV), 2009-11-09 (Box 6)
  - Tracy Volz / Sociology - Technology in the Classroom, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-11-16 (Box 6)
  - Dance #2, (DV), 2009-11-16 (Box 6)
  - Dance Remake #1, (DV), 2009-11-16 (Box 6)
  - Carlos Dance, camera 1, (DV), 2009-11-16 (Box 6)
  - Carlos Owl Socrates Meade, (DV), 2009-11-23 (Box 6)
  - Birth of a Racer Documentary, (DVD), 2009-11-24 (Box 6)
  - Leslie Campbell, Office Wikis and Podcasts, (DV), 2009-11-25 (Box 6)
  - Carlos Dr. Dick class Panopto, (DV), 2009-11-25 (Box 6)
  - Slogs - Holly Heard, (DV), 2009-12-04 (Box 6)
  - Holly Heard in office blogs, (DV), 2009-12-09 (Box 6)
  - Henry Wong / Garage Technology Ventures, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-12-10 (Box 6)
  - Leighton Read / Seriosity and Alloy Ventures, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-12-10 (Box 6)
  - Rice Alliance #1, (DV), 2009-12-10 (Box 6)
  - Rice Alliance #2, (DV), 2009-12-10 (Box 6)
  - Rice Alliance #3, (DV), 2009-12-10 (Box 6)
  - Shell Center, Hartley #1, (DV), 2009-12-21 (Box 6)
  - Gold Award 2010, Rice Media, (DVD) (Box 6)
  - SCS narration, Erin, (DV), 2010 (Box 6)
  - Basketball conference, Keck, (DV), 2010 (Box 6)
  - Michael Lindsay/ Selecting and Developing the Best (4), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010 (Box 6)
  - Legobots #2, (DV), 2010 (Box 6)
  - Matriculation 2010, (DV) (Box 6)
  - Boles, 80th birthday of willy statue, (DVD), 2010 (Box 6)
  - SCS, HARC, Bob Harris, (DV), 2010-01-11 (Box 6)
  - Alan D. Bersin and Geronimo Gutierrez Fernandez / U.S.-Mexico Border Security (3), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-01-13 (Box 6)
  - Shell Board Meeting #1, (DV), 2010-01-13 (Box 6)
  - Puentes #1 camera 1, (DV), 2010-01-14 (Box 6)
  - Puentes #2 camera 1, (DV), 2010-01-14 (Box 6)
  - Puentes #3 camera 1, (DV), 2010-01-14 (Box 6)
  - Puentes #4 camera 1, (DV), 2010-01-14 (Box 6)
  - Puentes standby, camera 1, (DV), 2010-01-14 (Box 6)
  - Puentes #1 camera 2, (DV), 2010-01-14 (Box 6)
  - Puentes #2 camera 2, (DV), 2010-01-14 (Box 6)
  - Puentes #3 camera 2, (DV), 2010-01-14 (Box 6)
  - Puentes #4 camera 2, (DV), 2010-01-14 (Box 6)
  - Puentes standby, camera 2, (DV), 2010-01-14 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk Anzali #1, (DV), 2010-01-19 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk Bhai? #2, (DV), 2010-01-19 (Box 6)
  - Mayor Annise Parker interview raw footage (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-01-20 (Box 6)
  - Holly Heard Blogs; Mayor Parker interview, (DVD), 2010-01-20 (Box 6)
  - Rice exteriors, (DV), 2010-01-20 (Box 6)
  - Annise Parker, (DV), 2010-01-20 (Box 6)
  - Gillis, Shell, (DV), 2010-01-25 (Box 6)
  - Rice B-roll, Walking, classes, misc., (DV), 2010-01-25 (Box 6)
  - B-Roll Stock Footage, Rice IT, (DVD), 2010-01-26 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk Jikh? #1 of 2, (DV), 2010-01-26 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk Sikhism #2, (DV), 2010-01-26 (Box 6)
  - SCS, Alan Chapman, (DV), 2010-01-29 (Box 6)
  - B-Roll Stock Footage: BRC, quad, gate, overhanging trees, Brochstein,McNair Hall, Baker Inst.; rec center with palm trees (6), Rice IT, (DVD), 2010-02 (Box 6)
  - B-Roll Backup of .mp4 files, Bloomberg (4), (DVD), 2010-02 (Box 6)
  - B-Roll Stock Footage, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-02 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk #1, (DV), 2010-02-16 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk #2, (DV), 2010-02-16 (Box 6)
  - Stephen Klineberg, SCS + Solar, (DV), 2010-02-17 (Box 6)
  - B-Roll for IBS/Bloomberg TV (4), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-02-20 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk 10 ZORO? #1, (DV), 2010-02-23 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk 10 ZORO? #2, (DV), 2010-02-23 (Box 6)
  - Ata Anzali / Zoroastrianism, (DVD), 2010-02-23 (Box 6)
  - B-roll Rec Center, (DV), 2010-02-24 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk #1, (DV), 2010-02-25 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk #2, (DV), 2010-02-25 (Box 6)
  - B-roll Rice Blogs, (DV), 2010-02-26 (Box 6)
  - B'nai Mitzvah of Daniel S. Leebron and Sydney G. Robinson, (DVD), 2010-02-27 (Box 6)
  - SCS, Windmills, (DV), 2010-03 (Box 6)
  - Gottschalk, Sky + City, (DV), 2010-03 (Box 6)
  - David [Del Pino] Project, Renata Ramos, (DV), 2010-03-03 (Box 6)
  - SCS, Keck Lab #1, (DV), 2010-03-09 (Box 6)
  - Students, Renata Ramos, (DV), 2010-03-11 (Box 6)
  - SCS, Mercury, (DV), 2010-03-17 (Box 6)
  - Rice statue anniversary, (DV), 2010-03-18 (Box 6)
  - Trojan/Alexander #1, (DV), 2010-03-22 (Box 6)
  - Trojan/Alexander #2, (DV), 2010-03-22 (Box 6)
  - David Alexander, (DVD), 2010-03-22 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk - Ann Gleig / Buddhism, (DVD), 2010-03-23 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk Buddhism #1, (DV), 2010-03-23 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk Buddhism #2, (DV), 2010-03-23 (Box 6)
  - Leebron Bar Mitzvah (2), (DVD), 2010-03-24 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk Hind Makki #1, (DV), 2010-03-24 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk Hind Makki #2, (DV), 2010-03-24 (Box 6)
  - SCS, Hamman, (DV), 2010-03-31 (Box 6)
  - BRC opening #1, (DV), 2010-04-01 (Box 6)
  - Holly Heard / Blogs, (DVD), 2010-04-05 (Box 6)
  - Shell CS, B-roll, (DV), 2010-04-05 (Box 6)
  - Scholarship banquet, Advancing Education, (DV), 2010-04-13 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk Holocaust Museum #1, (DV), 2010-04-13 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk Holocaust Museum #2, (DV), 2010-04-13 (Box 6)
  - SCS, Klineberg + class traffic[?], (DV), 2010-04-15 (Box 6)
  - [Sent for … Commish?] #2, (DV), 2010-04-16 (Box 6)
  - Centennial #3, (DV), 2010-04-16 (Box 6)
  - Centennial Plan #1, (DV), 2010-04-16 (Box 6)
  - SCS B-roll Galveston, (DV), 2010-04-17 (Box 6)
  - Trevisio #1, (DV), 2010-04-17 (Box 6)
  - Trevisio #2, (DV), 2010-04-17 (Box 6)
  - Trevisio #3, (DV), 2010-04-17 (Box 6)
  - Trevisio #4, (DV), 2010-04-17 (Box 6)
  - Mayor Annise Parker interview and Willie Statue Turn anniversary celebration (2) one so far, (DVD), 2010-04-19 (Box 6)
  - Allen Matusow [interview] #1, (DV), 2010-04-19 (Box 6)
  - Matusow interviews 2, (DV), 2010-05-11 (Box 6)
  - John Boles / Dr. Lovett and the Opening of Rice University unedited footage, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-05-15 (Box 6)
  - Boles/ BRC, (DV), 2010-05-15 (Box 6)
  - Shell Center for Sustainability Rough-cut, (DVD), 2010-05-20 (Box 6)
  - Boles talk, Woodson, (DV), 2010-05-27 (Box 6)
  - David del Pino IT Video Production, (DVD), 2010-06 (Box 6)
  - Building the BuckyBall / 25th anniversary Sand Castle (4), Killgore, (DVD), 2010-06-05 (Box 6)
  - NANO Beach #1, (DV), 2010-06-05 (Box 6)
  - NANO Beach #2, (DV), 2010-06-05 (Box 6)
  - John Boles on Centennial, (DVD), 2010-06-09 (Box 6)
  - John Boles / Upcoming Centennial Celebration Rough-cut, (DVD), 2010-06-10 (Box 6)
  - John Boles / Upcoming Centennial Celebration (3), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-06-10 (Box 6)
  - Shell Center for Sustainability Roughcut, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-06-11 (Box 6)
  - Apollo 13 Intro with Bill Broyles Rough-cut 1 (3), also "Raw P-Z files", Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-06-15 (Box 6)
  - Shell Center for Sustainability, Version 5, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-06-22 (Box 6)
  - David [Del Pino] Project, Ramos, (DV), 2010-06-23 (Box 6)
  - Shell Center for Sustainability (rough-cut) and Mayor Bill White speaking at Rice, (DVD), 2010-06-24 (Box 6)
  - Trojan Project, Siemann, (DV), 2010-06-28 (Box 6)
  - Educational Technologies Instructional Videos - BIOPAC (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-07-07 (Box 6)
  - Instructional Videos, Biopack, Rice HD B-roll, statue turning, (DVD), 2010-07-07 (Box 6)
  - David del Pino, BioPac, (DVD), 2010-07-07 (Box 6)
  - John Boles on Lovett/Opening, (DVD), 2010-07-12 (Box 6)
  - David del Pino, BioPac, EdTech, (DVD), 2010-07-20 (Box 6)
  - Michael Lindsay, tape 1, camera 2, (DV), 2010-07-20 (Box 6)
  - Michael Lindsay, camera 1, (DV), 2010-07-20 (Box 6)
  - Hector, McMurtry [Auditorium], raw footage, authored DVD, (DVD), 2010-08 (Box 6)
  - Rice IT photo short, (DV), 2010-08 (Box 6)
  - B-Roll Stock Footage - test (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-08-15 (Box 6)
  - Y. Ping Sun, David Leebron / Freshman Move-in (6), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-08-15 (Box 6)
  - B-Roll Stock Footage (4), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-08-15 (Box 6)
  - Freshmen move-in, Y. Ping Sun, B-roll #1, (DV), 2010-08-15 (Box 6)
  - Matriculation address #1, (DV), 2010-08-15 (Box 6)
  - B-Roll HD: buildings, students in class, etc., (DVD), 2010-08-26 (Box 6)
  - Rice HD B-Roll, (DVD), 2010-08-27 (Box 6)
  - ADVANCE #2, (DV), 2010-09-07 (Box 6)
  - Mikki Hebl ADVANCE #3, (DV), 2010-09-07 (Box 6)
  - Mikki Hebl ADVANCE #4, (DV), 2010-09-07 (Box 6)
  - Mikki Hebl ADVANCE #1of 1, (DV), 2010-09-07 (Box 6)
  - Mikki Hebl / Search Committee Training, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-09-08 (Box 6)
  - Odegard et al., B-roll, (DV), 2010-09-09 (Box 6)
  - B-roll for Gary K [Kidney] project, Manhole +, (DV), 2010-09-09 (Box 6)
  - B-roll, Gary K [Kidney], #3, (DV), 2010-09-09 (Box 6)
  - Rice Manhole B-Roll unedited footage, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-09-09 (Box 6)
  - New Pathways Towards Prosperity, Part 1 (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-09-14 (Box 6)
  - New Pathways Towards Prosperity, Part 2, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-09-14 (Box 6)
  - New Pathways Towards Prosperity, Part 4, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-09-14 (Box 6)
  - Cindy Farach-Carson / Stepping Stones: I Got By With a Little Help from My Friends, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-09-19 (Box 6)
  - Farac-Carson ADVANCE Pt1, (DV), 2010-09-19 (Box 6)
  - Mikki Hebl / Fear of Failure, Fear of Success (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-09-20 (Box 6)
  - Mikki Hebl ADVANCE #1of 1, (DV), 2010-09-20 (Box 6)
  - Tracy Volz ADVANCE #1: Technical Presentations (2, (DV), 2010-09-20 (Box 6)
  - Tracy Volz ADVANCE #2, (DV), 2010-09-20 (Box 6)
  - Mikki Hebl ADVANCE pt 2, (DV), 2010-09-20 (Box 6)
  - Colvin ADVANCE lunch #1, (DV), 2010-09-21 (Box 6)
  - Vicki Colvin: "Managing a Research Group - Lessons Learned", Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-09-21 (Box 6)
  - Trojan, Keck Lecture Hall, camera 1, (DV), 2010-09-30 (Box 6)
  - Trojan, Keck Lecture Hall, slides, camera 2, (DV), 2010-09-30 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk #1 of 1, (DV), 2010-10-08 (Box 6)
  - Hand Washer #1, (DV), 2010-10-10 (Box 6)
  - Leebron Town Hall #1, (DV), 2010-10-12 (Box 6)
  - Leebron Town Hall #2, (DV), 2010-10-12 (Box 6)
  - Centennial Kick-off #1, (DV), 2010-10-12 (Box 6)
  - Centennial Kick-off #2, (DV), 2010-10-12 (Box 6)
  - Research B-Roll: BRC and Other Labs, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-10-14 (Box 6)
  - BRC B-roll, (DV), 2010-10-14 (Box 6)
  - Tuskegee Airmen #1, (DV), 2010-10-24 (Box 6)
  - Tuskegee Airmen #2, (DV), 2010-10-24 (Box 6)
  - McMurtry College Dedication, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-10-29 (Box 6)
  - McMurtry College Dedication #1, (DV), 2010-10-29 (Box 6)
  - Leach #1, (DV), 2010-11-04 (Box 6)
  - Leach #2, (DV), 2010-11-04 (Box 6)
  - Centennial Committee #1, (DV), 2010-11-09 (Box 6)
  - Centennial Committee #2, (DV), 2010-11-09 (Box 6)
  - Zadie Smith lecture #1, (DV), 2010-11-11 (Box 6)
  - Sociology Meeting, Founders Room: Meeting and interviews unedited footage, Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-11-12 (Box 6)
  - Elizabeth Long, Elaine Ecklund, Sociology [1970] #1, (DV), 2010-11-12 (Box 6)
  - Sociology meeting [1970] #2, (DV), 2010-11-12 (Box 6)
  - Elevator Pitches unedited, unmixed (2), (DVD), 2010-11-18 (Box 6)
  - Duncan College Dedication (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2010-11-19 (Box 6)
  - Duncan College Dedication #1, (DV), 2010-11-19 (Box 6)
  - Robot Quiddich, (DVD), 2010-12 (Box 6)
  - Legobots #1, (DV), 2010-12-02 (Box 6)
  - Straum Boniuk #1, (DV), 2010-12-06 (Box 6)
  - Shell Sustainability Project, Anderson interview, (DV), 2010-12-06 (Box 6)
  - Chris Hight, Shell Nano, (DV), 2010-12-16 (Box 6)
  - Holly Heard Blogs [2009]; Mayor Parker interview, (DV), 2010-12-20 (Box 6)
  - Gold medals--Matusow, Curl, Brochstein; Duncan College Dedication, (DVD), 2010-2011 (Box 7)
  - IT Misc. Video Shorts, pt 1, Rice EdTech, (DVD) 2010-2012 (Box 7)
  - IT Misc. Video Shorts, pt 2, Rice EdTech, (DVD) 2010-2012 (Box 6)
  - 2011 Training, Part 3 (4), (DVD) (Box 7)
  - Beer-Bike 2011, Fonteno, McMurtry, (DVD) (Box 7)
  - Henry Rachford interview, (DVD), 2011 (Box 7)
  - Many Great Scans of Early Rice Stills from WRC, (DVD), 2011 (Box 7)
  - LAN projects, Lovett and baker, OEDK, Shell Program, Walking Tour, (DVD), 2011 (Box 7)
  - Brochstein artwork LH Vid, (DV), 2011 (Box 7)
  - Backup - KillianExplainsLab.Mov: Matusow Intro, Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-01-06 (Box 7)
  - Video Samples in progress, Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-01-18 (Box 7)
  - Rice 2032 Teaching, (DV), 2011-01-20 (Box 7)
  - Robots, Autism #2, (DV), 2011-01-25 (Box 7)
  - Robots Autism #1, (DV), 2011-01-25 (Box 7)
  - Sociology Meeting - Founders Room rough-cut, Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-02-01 (Box 7)
  - Steve Dvorak, Lovett Hall, (DV), 2011-02-07 (Box 7)
  - Jocelyn #1, (DV), 2011-02-10 (Box 7)
  - Annual Fund Volunteer Training, Session 1 (2), (DVD), 2011-02-12 (Box 7)
  - Annual Fund Volunteer Training, Session 2, (DVD), 2011-02-12 (Box 7)
  - Huff House #1, (DV), 2011-02-12 (Box 7)
  - Huff House #2, (DV), 2011-02-12 (Box 7)
  - Huff House #3, (DV), 2011-02-12 (Box 7)
  - Huff House #4, (DV), 2011-02-12 (Box 7)
  - Leebron Centennial Quote Redo, (DVD), 2011-02-14 (Box 7)
  - Lovett Hall building shots, (DV), 2011-02-15 (Box 7)
  - Stills - Melissa [Kean], (DV), 2011-02-15 (Box 6)
  - Hand Washer Video (2), (DVD), 2011-02-20 (Box 7)
  - Sociology Quotes (2), (DVD), 2011-02-22 (Box 7)
  - David Leebron / Town Hall Meeting (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-02-22 (Box 7)
  - David Leebron, Town Hall #1, (DV), 2011-02-22 (Box 7)
  - George Greanias, Lovett Hall, (DV), 2011-02-23 (Box 7)
  - Jim Crownover, Lovett Hall #1, (DV), 2011-02-23 (Box 7)
  - Dr. Wiernadi [Richard Wainerdi], Lovett Hall, (DV), 2011-02-24 (Box 7)
  - Stephen Klineberg, Neal Lane, Lovett Hall, (DV), 2011-02-24 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines II: Round Table Discussion (3), Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Discipliens II: Panel 1 (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines II: Panel 2, Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines II: Panel 3, Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines, Part 3, (DVD), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines R-1, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines R-2, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines R-3, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines R-4, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines R-5, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines R-6, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines L-1, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines L-2, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines L-3, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines L-5, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Emerging Disciplines L-6, EdTech, (DV), 2011-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Shell Center for Sustainability Video -- in Progress (3), Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-03 (Box 7)
  - Larry McMurtry talking about his time at Rice, (DVD), 2011-03-01 (Box 7)
  - Melissa Kean narration, Lovett Hall, (DV), 2011-03-01 (Box 7)
  - David Leebron, Lovett Hall, (DV), 2011-03-01 (Box 7)
  - Ed Emmett, Lovett Hall, (DV), 2011-03-03 (Box 7)
  - Annise Parker, Lovett Hall, (DV), 2011-03-03 (Box 7)
  - Mayor Parker announcement; Lovett Hall Centennial (2), (DVD), 2011-03-07 (Box 7)
  - Lovett Hall Centennial #1 Roughcut (2), (DVD), 2011-03-07 (Box 7)
  - Lovett Hall Centennial, (DV), 2011-03-07 (Box 7)
  - Scientia #1, (DV), 2011-03-09 (Box 7)
  - Scientia #2, (DV), 2011-03-09 (Box 7)
  - Steve Murdock, (DV), 2011-03-13 (Box 6)
  - Steve Murcock on his books, (DVD), 2011-03-14 (Box 7)
  - Ann Lugg Project #1, (DV), 2011-03-14 (Box 7)
  - Steve Murdock on his books, (DVD), 2011-03-14 (Box 7)
  - Lovett Hall Video March 2011 (4), Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-03-16 (Box 7)
  - Ann Lugg #1, (DV), 2011-03-18 (Box 7)
  - OEDK, (DV), 2011-03-21 (Box 7)
  - Shell Center for Sustainability, (DVD), 2011-03-22 (Box 7)
  - Lovett Hall Video short version, Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-03-23 (Box 7)
  - Brockman Hall Dedication, Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-03-24 (Box 7)
  - Ann Lugg, (DV ), 2011-03-29 (Box 7)
  - Shell Center Video in Progress (2), (DVD), 2011-03-31 (Box 7)
  - Mathukumalli Vidyasagar / Statistical Methods in Cancer Biology (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2011-04-01 (Box 7)
  - OEDK (7), (DVD), 2011-04-06 (Box 7)
  - Tom Lytle on McMurtry Set-up (3), (DVD), 2011-04-11 (Box 7)
  - Shell Center for Sustainability, (DVD), 2011-04-11 (Box 7)
  - Shell Center for Sustainability Short, (DVD), 2011-04-11 (Box 7)
  - Peter Loewen music, no podium yet, (DV), 2011-04-18 (Box 7)
  - Brian Riedel video clips, (DVD), 2011-04-20 (Box 7)
  - Brian Riedel C U #1, (DV), 2011-04-20 (Box 7)
  - Bill Barnett, Sarah Whiting, Brochstein, (DV), 2011-04-21 (Box 7)
  - Curl, Kathleen Matthews, Frank Tittel, (DV), 2011-04-28 (Box 7)
  - John Hutchinson, Brown Teaching Award, (DV), 2011-05-06 (Box 7)
  - Rachel Kimbro, Teaching Award, (DV), 2011-05-11 (Box 7)
  - Bob Curl and Raymond Brochstein gold medal videos (3), (DVD), 2011-05-21 (Box 7)
  - Justin Denny, Ed Tech Vid #1 of 1, (DV), 2011-06-01 (Box 7)
  - Elizabeth Eich, Shape up, (DV), 2011-06-08 (Box 7)
  - Kate Kirkland on Capt. Baker #1, (DV), 2011-06-10 (Box 7)
  - David Caprette, Shape up, (DV), 2011-06-22 (Box 7)
  - [Annise Parker] at leadership forum, (DV), 2011-06-28 (Box 7)
  - Wetlands Mayor Parker clip, (DVD), 2011-06-30 (Box 7)
  - Jones Commons, (DV), 2011-07-05 (Box 7)
  - Brian Riedel Rough-cut, (DVD), 2011-07-22 (Box 7)
  - Beason class scale up, (DV), 2011-08-24 (Box 7)
  - Scale up Jones, (DV), 2011-08-29 (Box 7)
  - Scale-up (3), (DVD), 2011-08-31 (Box 7)
  - Richard Tapia / Crisis in Texas Higher Education, Killgore, (DVD), 2011-09-21 (Box 7)
  - John Boles on Books (2), (DVD), 2011-10 (Box 7)
  - Stephen Fox on Ralph Adams Cram, (DVD), 2011-10-01 (Box 7)
  - Boles on Books [that Shaped My World], (DV), 2011-10-05 (Box 7)
  - Boles #2, (DV), 2011-10-05 (Box 7)
  - Kate Kirkland on Capt. Baker, (DVD), 2011-10-06 (Box 7)
  - Lynn Ragsdale / V2C Gateway (3), (DVD), 2011-10-10 (Box 7)
  - Lynn Ragsdale, (DV), 2011-10-10 (Box 7)
  - Dawkins #1, (DV), 2011-10-10 (Box 7)
  - Dawkins #2, (DV), 2011-10-10 (Box 7)
  - Boles #1 (2), (DV), 2011-10-13 (Box 7)
  - Boles #2, (DV), 2011-10-13 (Box 7)
  - Boles Redux, (DV), 2011-10-13 (Box 7)
  - Scientia, Sewall #1, (DV), 2011-10-18 (Box 7)
  - Scientia, (DV), 2011-10-18 (Box 7)
  - Boniuk #1, (DV), 2011-10-19 (Box 7)
  - Boniuk #2, (DV), 2011-10-19 (Box 7)
  - [Stephen?] Fox #1, (DV), 2011-10-20 (Box 7)
  - [Stephen?] Fox #2, (DV), 2011-10-20 (Box 7)
  - Sally Ride #1, (DV), 2011-10-22 (Box 7)
  - Religion in University #1, (DV), 2011-11-04 (Box 7)
  - Religion in University #2, (DV), 2011-11-04 (Box 7)
  - Patel, Duncan, (DV), 2011-11-17 (Box 7)
  - David Leebron, scale up quote, (DV), 2011-11-21 (Box 7)
  - Justin Denny clips class, (DVD), 2011-11-22 (Box 7)
  - Justin Denny, (DV), 2011-11-22 (Box 7)
  - Teaching with Technology, EdTech Video, (DVD), 2011-11-29 (Box 7)
  - Sociology faculty interviews, (DV), 2011-12-13 (Box 7)
  - Rice Engineering Promo Video (2), (DVD), 2012 (Box 7)
  - Carolyn Johnson, College in 2020, (DV), 2012-01-13 (Box 7)
  - Leebron with Faculty Senate: Building the Vision in Disruptive Times, (DVD), 2012-01-20 (Box 7)
  - ECE Dist Lec #1, (DV), 2012-01-31 (Box 7)
  - ECE Lec #2, (DV), 2012-01-31 (Box 7)
  - Space Frontiers #1, (DV), 2012-02-16 (Box 7)
  - Virgil Wood / MLK (Here Project), (DVD), 2012-02-20 (Box 7)
  - Dr. [Virgil] Wood HERE lecture, (DV), 2012-02-20 (Box 7)
  - DeLange Conference Rawlings, (DVD), 2012-02-28 (Box 7)
  - David Leebron, Town Hall #1, (DV), 2012-03-07 (Box 7)
  - David Leebron, Town Hall #2, (DV), 2012-03-07 (Box 7)
  - President's House, Faculty Senate, (DV), 2012-03-09 (Box 7)
  - David Del Pino, Physics Lecture #1, (DV), 2012-03-27 (Box 7)
  - PLS, Ed Wilson #1, (DV), 2012-04-03 (Box 7)
  - PLS, Ed Wilson, (DV), 2012-04-03 (Box 7)
  - [Stanley Fish] Campbell Lecture #1, (DV), 2012-04-10 (Box 7)
  - [Stanley Fish] Campbell Lecture #2, (DV), 2012-04-10 (Box 7)
  - Stanley Fish, part 2, (DVD), 2012-04-11 (Box 7)
  - Stanley Fish #1, (DV), 2012-04-11 (Box 7)
  - Stanley Fish #2, (DV), 2012-04-11 (Box 7)
  - [Stanley Fish] Campbell Lecture #1, (DV), 2012-04-12 (Box 7)
  - [Stanley Fish] Campbell Lecture #2, (DV), 2012-04-12 (Box 7)
  - Leebron with Faculty Senate, (DVD), 2012-04-23 (Box 7)
  - Boniuk #1, (DV), 2012-05-01 (Box 7)
  - COURSERA Class Introductions: Johnson, Hutchinson, Warren, Rixner, Colvin (3), Rice EdTech, (DVD), 2012-06-01 (Box 7)
  - EdTech Video: Employing GPS Technology (2), (DVD), 2012-07-14 (Box 7)
  - EdTech Video: Employing GPS Technology: Tropical Field Biology (3), (DVD), 2012-07-16 (Box 7)
  - EdTech Video: Employing GPS Technology: Tropical Field Biology Belize (2), (DVD), 2012-07-16 (Box 7)
  - Common Reading #1, (DV), 2012-08-21 (Box 7)
  - Common Reading #2, (DV), 2012-08-21 (Box 7)
  - John Hutchinson; SeaLab Classrooms at Rice; Hands-on Archaeology (2), (DVD), 2012-09 (Box 7)
  - EdTech Video: Guy Almes interview, (DVD), 2012-09-05 (Box 7)
  - Elaine Ecklund / Religion in Global Context, (DVD), 2012-09-11 (Box 7)
  - Elaine Ecklund Redo Intro, (DV), 2012-09-18 (Box 7)
  - Scientia, RMC #1, (DV), 2012-09-18 (Box 7)
  - Scientia, RMC #2, (DV), 2012-09-18 (Box 7)
  - Nancy Hopkins, Keck 100, (DV), 2012-09-21 (Box 7)
  - Nancy Hopkins, Keck 100 #2, (DV), 2012-09-21 (Box 7)
  - Mikki Hebl, (DV), 2012-10-01 (Box 7)
  - Mikki Hebl #2, (DV), 2012-10-01 (Box 7)
  - Scientia, Brochstein #1, (DV), 2012-10-12 (Box 7)